JULY 15TH (THURS) 4:43 PM
It's open. Come in.
Rohan-sensei?
Where…
I'm here, Koichi.
Rohan-sensei!
What's wrong? You didn't mention
any of this over the phone…
I need your help.
An enemy Stand has its hold on me.
What?!
A S-Stand? Where is it? Where?!
It's on my back.
It's adhered itself to my back.
Your back?
Um… So this thing has
taken hold of your back?
Yes. This is very serious,
and I'm not sure what to do.
Could you show it to me?
There's no way.
But if you don't show it to me…
If I expose my back,
it'll kill me and take hold of you.
Quickly, burn them, yes?
See? It's talking!
This is what
I'm talking about, Koichi!
Huh?
Why are you hiding it?!
Is this all just some big joke?
How could you say that?!
I told you,
if I expose my back to you I die!
But how do I know you're not just
pulling my leg like you always do.
That is what you're up to, right…
No! I'm being dead serious!
There's a dead body upstairs!
Huh? A dead body?!
Um… What are you doing, Sensei?
Just step around me
and go on ahead.
Please, please, go ahead. Please!
What is all this about?
Well? Now do you believe me?
It's gone!
There's no way…
He's right here, Koichi!
Look, Koichi!
This is Masazo Kinoto!
He's been turned into
a lifeless husk!
Wow, that's some impressive work.
You know,
this isn't exactly the time
to be horsing around, Sensei!
Those Stand users the old man
in the photograph made
are trying to hunt us down
as we speak.
I rushed all the way over here
because I was worried something
may've happened to you!
What?
Then this thing…
Anyway, just be careful.
Bye.
W-Wait, Koichi!
I called you over here
because I knew those pieces of shit
Josuke and Okuyasu would
have another moronic laugh fest!
You have to believe me!
I thought we were friends!
Koichi!
Cheer up now, yes?
It's natural to be
a little disheartened…
I have never been
more humiliated in my life…
You bastard. You'll pay for this…
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us